For example, different rooms.
The more defined places are apart, the easier it will be.
Go for a walk through your palace
And place what you need to remember!
For example, if you have to remember different types of vertebrates
can you imagine a snake to rush out
Under that old office standing out in the hall
Imagine what it looks like,
How the mountain feels.
When you then move on into the kitchen
Do you see that the kitchen doors have become bird cages.
When you open the cabinet, a pigeon flashes.
Visualize how it sounds, feels or smells.
The more in -depth you imagine things,
The easier they will be to remember.
When you then sit on a sample
Can you go through your "palace" mentally.
Stop in the different places and pick up the fact that is connected to the site.
It is important that you follow a definite route,
sight, taste, hearing, feeling and smell
We perceive information.
So when you are going to learn something new,
Try to use as many senses as possible.
Then it becomes easier to remember!
Had you just said crawfish in the hall
And birds in the kitchen would not have become as strong.
Make the pictures in your palace as vivid as you can!
How or where you place the knowledge
does not have to be logical or useful for someone else.
The method works better